WILBERT BOADZO

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Markwei Majele Loope no.9 Spintex, 00233 Ghana

PHONE

0542422691

EMAIL

wilbertboadzo144@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

15/04/1999 37 Military Hospital - Accra

NATIONALITY

Ghanaian

LINKS

LinkedIn

SKILLS

Ability to Work in a Team

• • • •

Network Troubleshooting

• • 0 0 0

Cisco Networking

• • 0 0 0

Html

• • • 0 0

Linux

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

GitHub

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Javascript

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

C programming

• • 0 0 0

Cisco Packet Tracer

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

PROFILE

Highly motivated Junior Network Engineer with experience in designing, implementing, and maintaining computer networks. Proficient in TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, VLANs, and routing, with experience configuring network hardware and software, collaborating with other IT professionals, and providing technical support to users and team members.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Real Estate Advertiser, Gordon's Properties

Accra

May 2019 — Jul 2021

- Promoted sales of properties through advertisements, open houses, and participation in multiple listing services.
- · Coordinated appointments to show homes to prospective buyers.
- Managed online advertising campaigns through social media, developing ads and creative assests whiles managing budget and performance metrics.
- Slashed payroll/benefits administration costs 30% by negotiating pricing and fees, while ensuring the continuation and enhancements of services."

Wordpress Developer, Social Edge Africa

Accra

Feb 2021 — Oct 2022

- Worked directly with clients, providing consultation, technical support and troubleshooting assistance.
- Managed WordPress websites, monitoring site performance and providing support to clients and users.
- Coordinated with clients, stakeholders and team members to define Wordpress project scope, timelines and deliverables ensuring successful timely completion.

EDUCATION

Basic Education, 5th Battalion Infantry

Burma Camp

Jun 2014

Graduated with a Basic Education Certificate

General Arts, St John's Grammar Senior High

Nov 2014 — Apr 2017

Graduated with a West African Education Certicate in General Arts

Software Engineering, Holberton School

Accra

Nov 2022 — Present

This is Software Engineering programme to study full stack development

Network Engineering, Kenyatta University

May 2023

CCNA 1: Introduction to Networking Certificate

Introduction to Networks course and can proficiently;

- Configure switches and end devices to provide access to local and remote network resources.
- Explain how physical and data link layer protocols support the operation of Ethernet in a switched network.
- · Configure routers to enable end-to-end connectivity between remote devices
- · Explain how the upper layers of the OSI model support network.

CCNA 2: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essentials Certificate

Acquired the skills to confidently;

- · Configure VLANs and Inter-VLAN routing applying security best practices.
- · Troubleshoot inter-VLAN routing on Layer 3 devices.
- · Configure redundancy on a switched network using STP and EtherChannel
- · Configure switch security to mitigate LAN attacks.
- · Configure IPv4 and IPv6 static routing on routers

CCNA 3: Enterprise Networking, Security, and Automation Certificate

Achieved skills to proficiently;

- · Explain how to mitigate threats and enhance network security using
- · access control lists and security best practices.
- Implement standard IPv4 ACLs to filter traffic and secure administrative access.
- \cdot Configure NAT services on the edge router to provide IPv4 address scalability.
- Explain how to optimize, monitor, and troubleshoot scalable network architecture

REFERENCES

Mr Gideon Osabutey from Social Edge Africa

gidofori@gmail.com | +233555175013

Gordon Bortekwei Dodoo from Gordon's Properties

+233245425735